[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Epic Movie the character named Edward parodies the movie Nacho Libre.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where did the first reported attacks of the legendary blood-sucking creature called Chupacabra occur?", "correct_answer": "Puerto Rico", "incorrect_answers": ["Brazil", "Texas, USA", "Nicaragua"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character did Danny DeVito voice in the 1997 animated movie Hercules?", "correct_answer": "Philoctetes", "incorrect_answers": ["Hades", "Hercules", "Zeus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid released?", "correct_answer": "1969", "incorrect_answers": ["1970", "1967", "1968"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If he loved you with all the power of his soul for a whole lifetime, he couldnt love you as much as I do in a single day. (1992)", "correct_answer": "Wuthering Heights", "incorrect_answers": ["Romeo and Juliet", "Shakespeare in Love", "Sideways"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Because of the Greenhouse Effect, Venus has the hottest surface temperature in the Solar System. What is the average temperature on Venus?", "correct_answer": "460 Degrees C.", "incorrect_answers": ["1,200 Degrees C.", "135 Degrees C.", "800 Degrees C."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which disorder is characterised by a fear of the number 13?", "correct_answer": "Triskaidekaphobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Caligynephobia", "Anglophobia", "Xylophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What river, draining into the Caspian Sea, is the longest in Europe?", "correct_answer": "Volga", "incorrect_answers": ["Danube", "Ural", "Dnieper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these serial murderers was nicknamed The Vampire of Sacramento, as he drank the blood and ate the remains of his victims?", "correct_answer": "Richard Chase", "incorrect_answers": ["Joseph Paul Franklin", "Joe Ball", "Jeffrey Dahmer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "David Letterman screen tested for the role of Ted Striker in the movie Airplane!, ultimately played by Robert Hays.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Three of these people were competitors and / or critics of Newton.  Can you spot the odd one?", "correct_answer": "Issac Barrow", "incorrect_answers": ["Gottfried Leibnitz", "Christian Huygens", "Robert  Hooke"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these countries is the largest producer and consumer of cows milk in the world?", "correct_answer": "India", "incorrect_answers": ["United States", "South Africa", "China"]}]